export default data = [
  {
      question: "The temple stages performances of Taiwanese opera every year as an expression of _____ to the Goddess of Mercy.",
      options: ["caution","gratitude","approval","dignity"],
      correct_option: "gratitude"
  },
  {
      question: "All the students are required to attend the two-day ________ program so that they can have a complete understanding of the university they are admitted to.",
      options: ["orientation","accomplishment","enthusiasm","independence"],
      correct_option: "orientation"
  },
  {
      question: "The _____ of his new album has brought the pop singer a huge fortune as well as worldwide fame.  ",
      options: ["salary","release","bargain","harvest"],
      correct_option: "release"
  },
  {
      question: "One important purpose of the course is for the students to learn to make sound judgments so that they can ________ between fact and opinion without difficulty. ",
      options: ["inform","undertake","manipulate","differentiate"],
      correct_option: "differentiate"
  },
  {
      question: "In Taiwan, using electronic devices is prohibited on domestic flights because it _____ with the communication between the pilots and the control tower. ",
      options: ["occupies","activates","interferes","eliminates"],
      correct_option: "interferes"
  },
  {
      question: "The famous actress decided to sue the magazine for purposely ________ what she actually said and did at the party.",
      options: ["assigning","contributing","foreseeing","distorting"],
      correct_option: "distorting"
  },
  {
      question: "The little boy is very ________: he is interested in a lot of different things and always wants to find out more about them. ",
      options: ["accurate","inquisitive","manageable","contemporary"],
      correct_option: "inquisitive"
  },
  {
      question: "The tourists enjoyed wholeheartedly the ________ scenery along the coast highway between Hualien and Ilan.",
      options: ["airtight","breathtaking","sentimental","eccentric"],
      correct_option: "breathtaking"
  },
  {
      question: "The major theme in the ____ issue of the best-selling monthly magazine will be “Love and Peace.”  ",
      options: ["forthcoming","expensive","brilliant","ambitious"],
      correct_option: "forthcoming"
  },
  {
      question: "Our English teacher always emphasizes the importance of learning new words in context rather than learning each of them _____.",
      options: ["individually","exclusively","approximately","supposedly"],
      correct_option: "individually"
  },
  {
      question: "The old woman at the street corner must be lost. She is looking around ________ for someone to help her.",
      options: ["socially","accidentally","tremendously","desperately"],
      correct_option: "desperately"
  },
  {
      question: "John is an experienced salesperson. Just observe closely how he interacts with customers and do ___. Then you will become an expert yourself. ",
      options: ["edgewise","likewise","otherwise","clockwise"],
      correct_option: "likewise"
  },
  {
      question: "A variety of preventive measures are now _____ in order to minimize the potential damage caused by the deadly disease.",
      options: ["by birth","at will","in place","on call"],
      correct_option: "in place"
  },
  {
      question: "With over fifty teams competing in the tournament, all the games will be played ________.",
      options: ["eye to eye","head to toe","hand to mouth","back to back"],
      correct_option: "back to back"
  },
  {
      question: "Did I say “a lot of dime”? Oh, I’m really sorry. I meant to say “a lot of time.” It was a ________. ",
      options: ["slip of the tongue","thorn in my side","penny for your thoughts","leap in the dark"],
      correct_option: "slip of the tongue"
  },
]